

Flushing, NY • tiffany lo[at]icloud.com

WWW tiffanylo.dev • LINKEDIN /tiffanylocodes • GITHUB /missamii

"Before attending General Assembly. At twelve years old I was already dabbling heavily in design + code. Today, my mission is to create a beautiful web and to use sustainable tech to accomplish this. I am the people's Developer who advocates for user experience."

SKILLS

HTML5/CSS3 • PHP • Ruby • JavaScript • ¡Query • ES6 • Ruby on Rails • PostgreSQL MongoDB • SQL • MySQL • React.JS • Express • Node.JS • API • Paint Shop Pro X •

Web Hosting • FTP • Greensock

## **EXPERIENCE**

05.2018 - current CHAYN Global • Executive Director & Front End Developer

02.2018 - 05.2018 Content Writer & Social Media

12.2017 - 06.2018 2 Market Media Remote • Freelance Front End Developer

Creates and maintains landing pages and websites. Using a range of technologies such as-PHP, HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

08.2017 - 08.2017 CiFiCo Melville, NY • JavaScript Animator

Animated SVGs and created SVGs. Using pure vanilla JavaScript and a third-party animation library, Greensock. Front End: CSS, HTML5, Javascript, Greensock library.

03.2017 - 08.2017 Global Telecom Supply Roslyn, NY • Full Stack Web Developer

Created and maintain their website and backend. I brought to them their first and official in house code base. Front End: JavaScript & jQuery, Bootstrap, HTML/CSS. Back End: PHP, MySQL/SQL, JavaScript.

11.2016 - current Tiffany Lo Designs Remote • Full Stack Web Developer Freelancer

I present my client's with attractive, functional websites and applications to make their products and services stand out to a wide audience. Using a range of technologies to make their goals a reality. Past Client(s): Kyle Moore - Theme for Website; Frontend: HTML, CSS, W3.CSS framework. Backend: PHP, MySQL & Landing Page; Frontend: ¡Query, Bulma framework.

## **VOLUNTEER**

02.2017 - 03.2017 ScriptEd Inc. The Young Women's Leadership School, New York, NY • Academic Web Developer Gave high school students a push and introduction into STEM. Laving down the fundamen-

tals of HTML, CSS and JavaScript. So they can be equipped to build their own websites and games.

## **EDUCATION**

General Assembly New York, NY • Full Stack Web Development The Art Institute of New York City New York, NY • Graphic Design